Guide to the Cable 13 Videotapes, 1976-2009 UA.09.13.0008
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2016-0027, 1976-2009; 2
  - AI Symposium Lecture: Dr. Tennett, 1985 (Box 28, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0020)
    Program Length: 35mins1sec; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2; Other notes: Part 1
  - AI Symposium Lecture: Dr. Tennett, 1985 (Box 28, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0021)
    Program Length: 50mins35secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 3; Other notes: Part 2
  - AI Symposium Lecture: Bruce G. Buchanan, 1985 (Box 28, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0022)
    Program Length: 45mins44secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 4
  - AI Symposium Lecture: Dr. Fox, 1985 (Box 28, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0023)
    Program Length: 38mins5secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 5
  - AI Symposium Lecture: Dr. Feigenbaum, 1985 (Box 28, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0024)
    Program Length: 46mins15secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 6
  - Something to Thing About, 1985 December (Box 30, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0215)
    Cable13 tape number: 2; Other notes: South Africa, Produced by Betsy Hadden
  - Brodie Inauguration, 1985 Fall (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0216)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (3); Other notes: Raw footage
  - Special Events: The Company of "Company", 1985 October (Box 28, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0229)
    Program Length: 20mins; Other notes: The Making of a Musical, Crew: Chris Klugewicz, Mark Rogers
  - Military vs. the Media, 1985 Spring (Box 24, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0237)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: ST 73; Other notes: Debate between representatives of US armed forces and students of PPS course
  - Military vs. the Media, 1985 Spring (Box 25, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0238)
    Program Length: 25mins; Cable13 tape number: ST 74; Other notes: Scenario 2: Military deployment and Media Access
  - Military vs. the Media, 1985 Spring (Box 25, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0239)
    Program Length: 47mins; Cable13 tape number: ST 75; Other notes: Scenario 3: Threat of War
  - Happenings Spring 1985, 1985 Spring (Box 25, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0240)
    Program Length: 22mins23secs; Cable13 tape number: ST 76; Other notes: Comedy interviews, crew: David Saunders, Bernie Schramm
  - Life on the Quad, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0241)
    Program Length: 17min30secs; Cable13 tape number: E2; Other notes: Episode 2
  - Life on the Quad, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0242)
    Program Length: 17mins; Cable13 tape number: E4; Other notes: Episode 4, Marsha dies
  - Life on the Quad, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0243)
    Program Length: 18mins; Cable13 tape number: E5; Other notes: Episode 5, Drama, Frat parties
  - Life on the Quad, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0244)
    Program Length: 20mins; Cable13 tape number: E7; Other notes: Episode 7 Lover's Quarrel Scene, Jay Bilas in scene
  - Life on the Quad, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0245)
    Cable13 tape number: E8; Other notes: Episode 8
  - Life on the Quad, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0246)
    Cable13 tape number: E9 & 9 1/2; Other notes: Episode 9 & 9 1/2
  - Life on the Quad, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0247)
    Program Length: 10mins; Cable13 tape number: E10; Other notes: Episode 10 cuts off in the middle
  - Basketball: Duke vs Harvard, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0248)
    Program Length: 20mins
  - Duke Yearlook, 1985 (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0003)
  - Entertainment: Greek Follies, 1985 January 13 (Box 24, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0221)
    Cable13 tape number: E 27-A; Other notes: Sorority Rush
  - Entertainment: Greek Follies, 1985 January 13 (Box 24, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0222)
    Cable13 tape number: E 27-B; Other notes: Sorority Rush
  - Sports Center Sunday, 1985 February 03, 1985 February 24 (Box 23, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0217)
    Program Length: 34mins18secs; Cable13 tape number: ST 70; Other notes: 2/3/85: Mark Militello, Dede Zeluck, Jay Bilas, Guest: Noel Patterson, Jim Cabrera 2/24/85 Guest: James Easton, Jeff Hersch
  - Special Events: Soviet Dissident, 1985 February 06 (Box 24, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0218)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1)
  - Interviews w/ Sherideth S. Rhompal, 1985 February 12 (Box 24, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0219)
    Other notes: Rhompal, Secretary General of Commonwealth, Speaker at 3rd World Conf., by T. Day
  - Sports Center, 1985 February 17 (Box 23, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0220)
    Program Length: 22mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1); Other notes: Guest: Nancy Hogshead
  - Frame by Frame: A Video Anthology, 1985 March 23 (Box 102, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0223)
    Cable13 tape number: copy 2; Other notes: w/ Jules Olitski, Coffeehouse commercial, Tribute to Stranger than Paradise, Dave Meyer's Band Music Video
  - Fashion Interview by Helen Freeman, 1985 April 03 (Box 17, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0214)
    Program Length: 27mins; Other notes: Mary McFadden(designer), Gene Pressman(Barney's N.Y.), Nian Hyde(Washington Post)
  - Soccer: Duke vs Indiana, 1985 September 05 (Box 27, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0235)
    Program Length: 62mins24secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1); Other notes: Roommate Game #1
  - Sports Center, 1985 September 29 (Box 26, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0236)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1); Other notes: w/ Jay Bilas and Mark Augusti
  - Body Works: Blue Devil, 1985 October 04 (Box 32, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0230)
    Program Length: 27mins30secs; Other notes: Amy Kwak, Moira Quinlan
  - Interviews w/ Robert F. Erburu, 1985 October 09 (Box 28, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0231)
    Program Length: 22mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1; Other notes: Erburu (Pres and CEO of Times Mirror) Crew: David Oelsner, Kevin Brooks, Carol Naslund
  - Sports Center, 1985 October 27 (Box 26, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0232)
    Program Length: 29mins41secs; Cable13 tape number: Show Tape
  - No Pretensions, 1985 October 29 (Box 25, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0233)
    Program Length: 23mins; Cable13 tape number: E 5; Other notes: Episode 5 Crew: Liza Mortimer, Carol Naslund
  - Interviews w/ John H. Sununu, 1985 October 31 (Box 28, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0234)
    Program Length: 13mins; Other notes: Sununu (Governor of New Hampshire) Interviewer: Helen Freeman, Crew: David Oelsner
  - Sports Center Sunday, 1985 November 03 (Box 39, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0224)
    Other notes: Interview with Coach Sloan
  - Sports Center, 1985 November 10 (Box 26, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0225)
    Program Length: 20mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1)
  - Soccer: Duke vs UNC, 1985 November 10 (Box 27, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0226)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1); Other notes: blacked tape
  - Duke Magazine, 1985 November 12 (Box 29, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0227)
    Cable13 tape number: Show #4; Other notes: Devil's Quarters, Union/Galleries, Uncle Al's What's Hot/What's Not, Mickey Mouse Clock, Sally Swenson-painting in Bryan Center
  - Sports Center, 1985 November 17 (Box 27, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0228)
    Program Length: 45mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1)
  - Life on the Quad, 1986 (Box 26, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0025)
    Cable13 tape number: E11; Other notes: Spring 1986
  - Basketball: First Round NCAA, 1986 (Box 28, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0026)
    Cable13 tape number: tape 1
  - Lipsync, 1986 (Box 29, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0027)
    Program Length: 53mins42secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (3); Other notes: Produced by Mary Rogers
  - Lipsync, 1986 (Box 29, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0028)
    Program Length: 55mins30secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (3)
  - Lipsync, 1986 (Box 29, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0029)
    Program Length: 55mins57secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 3 (3); Other notes: Dave Roberson Univ. Council
  - T&A Productions: Duke Soccer '86, 1986 (Box 34, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0030)
    Cable13 tape number: L14/S3; Other notes: by Alan Bushnell and Trux Dole
  - Sports Center Sunday, 1986 (Box 38, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0031)
    Other notes: 3/16, 11/9, 12/7/86 Hilites
  - Night Night Shows 4 & 5, 1986 (Box 77, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0032)
    Program Length: 30mins27secs
  - B-Ball NCAA Final: Duke vs Louisville, 1986 (Box 102, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0033)
    Program Length: 45mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1); Other notes: Feed from CBS, No audio
  - Hoof n' Horn: Anything Goes, 1986 April (Box 29, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0249)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Part 1 of 2
  - Hoof n' Horn: Anything Goes, 1986 April (Box 29, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0250)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Part 2 of 2
  - Fuqua Looks at Business, 1986 January 01 (Box 27, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0266)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2); Other notes: Fuqua Follies First Act, Bid Night
  - Night Night, 1986 Spring (Box 25, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0295)
    Program Length: 18mins28secs; Cable13 tape number: Edit Tape #9; Other notes: comedy skits, Karl Straub
  - Speakers: William Westmoreland, 1986 Spring (Box 29, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0296)
    Program Length: 60mins34secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2)
  - Speakers: William Westmoreland, 1986 Spring (Box 29, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0297)
    Program Length: 12mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2)
  - Best of Night Night 1986, 1986 Spring (Box 32, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0298)
    Program Length: 29mins; Other notes: compiled by D. Lammey 1/21/87, Intro '87, quad squad #1, News #2, Mr. X, Food Tiger Commercial, Beer Commercial, News #4
  - Speakers: Al McGuire, 1986 Spring (Box 39, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0299)
    Program Length: 44mins33secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2)
  - Speakers: Al McGuire, 1986 Spring (Box 39, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0300)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2)
  - Cyrus X, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0301)
    Program Length: 4mins55secs; Cable13 tape number: #4b; Other notes: continuation of an interview and final credits, copy of 8 movie footage salvaged from damaged tape
  - Cyrus X, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0302)
    Cable13 tape number: #5
  - Cyrus X, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0303)
    Program Length: 35mins45secs; Cable13 tape number: #9; Other notes: plus commercials
  - 1986-87 Sports Highlights, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0304)
    Program Length: 14mins30secs; Cable13 tape number: L13/S4
  - Fuqua Looks at Business, 1986-1987 (Box 37, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0305)
    Program Length: 56mins30secs; Other notes: 4/11/87: Final Show of '86-'87 season, 00-24:50, 10/11/87 24:58-43:40, 3/28/87, 43:40-56:30
  - Basketball: Highlights, 1986-1987 (Box 101, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0306)
  - Duke Yearlook, 1986 (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0004)
  - Basketball: Duke vs St. Louis, 1986 January 08 (Box 28, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0267)
  - Bishop D. Tutu in Chapel, 1986 January 19 (Box 29, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0268)
  - Sports Center, 1986 January 19 (Box 38, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0269)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1)
  - Sports Center Sunday, 1986 January 26 (Box 27, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0270)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1); Other notes: Guest: Billy King
  - Speakers: Adolfo Callero, 1986 January 28 (Box 30, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0271)
  - Sports Center, 1986 February 02 (Box 27, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0255)
  - Joseph Bryan's 90th Birthday, 1986 February 11 (Box 26, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0256)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2)
  - Joseph Bryan's 90th Birthday, 1986 February 11 (Box 26, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0257)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2)
  - Sports Center Sunday, 1986 February 16 (Box 27, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0258)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1); Other notes: Highlights of Hockey Game
  - No Pretensions, 1986 February 18 (Box 25, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0259)
    Cable13 tape number: E 1; Other notes: First Show, Second Semester
  - Basketball: Duke vs Miami, 1986 February 19 (Box 28, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0260)
    Program Length: 45mins; Cable13 tape number: tape 2
  - Basketball: Duke vs Miami, 1986 February 19 (Box 28, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0261)
    Program Length: 43mins46secs; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1
  - Night Night, 1986 February 22 (Box 25, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0262)
    Program Length: 21mins4secs; Other notes: comedy skits
  - Fuqua Looks at Business, 1986 February 22 (Box 42, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0263)
    Program Length: 30mins
  - Sports Center, 1986 February 23, 1986 March 16 (Box 27, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0264)
    Program Length: 45mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2); Other notes: w/ Jay Bilas, ends with lottery for NCAA tickets
  - No Pretensions, 1986 February 25 (Box 25, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0265)
  - Basketball: Duke vs UNC, 1986 March 02 (Box 37, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0272)
    Program Length: 20mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2); Other notes: Senior ceremony at beginning
  - Basketball: Duke vs UNC, 1986 March 02 (Box 37, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0273)
    Program Length: 20mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2); Other notes: Final game highlights
  - Body Works w/ Moira and Kristin, 1986 March 14 (Box 33, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0274)
    Program Length: 29mins
  - Sports Center, 1986 March 16 (Box 27, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0275)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2 (2); Other notes: Crew: Alan, Suzanne, Karl, Greg, Jeremy
  - Interviews w/ Willy Smith and Mark Bozek, 1986 March 21 (Box 29, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0276)
    Program Length: 32mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1; Other notes: Smith (fashion designer)
  - Fuqua Looks at Business, 1986 March 22 (Box 43, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0277)
    Program Length: 21mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1
  - Fuqua Looks at Business, 1986 March 29 (Box 25, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0278)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1
  - Sports Center Sunday, 1986 March 30 (Box 28, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0279)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1; Other notes: Talking about Final Four, Crew: Hal Schwartz, Mark Roberts, Beaker
  - Springfest, 1986 April 04 (Box 92, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0251)
    Cable13 tape number: L33/S5; Other notes: Tape 4 (4)
  - Sports Center Sunday, 1986 April 06 (Box 27, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0252)
    Cable13 tape number: Show Tape; Other notes: Screw Tape Corp, Gregg -- Take-off
  - Control Room Make-Over, Renovations, 1986 Summer (Box 101, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0954)
  - Basketball: Duke vs George Mason, 1986 September 17 (Box 34, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0294)
    Program Length: 46mins13secs; Cable13 tape number: L13/S1
  - Cyrus X, 1986 October 15 (Box 30, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0288)
    Cable13 tape number: Promo; Other notes: Steve Singer, Jim Balis
  - Cyrus X, 1986 October 15 (Box 30, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0289)
    Program Length: 38mins; Other notes: Producer Jim Balis
  - Special Events: Robert McNamara, 1986 October 16 (Box 23, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0290)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1; Other notes: by David Oelsner and Steve Tell
  - Football: Duke vs Maryland, 1986 October 25 (Box 33, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0291)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 3; Other notes: Homecoming
  - Sports Center, 1986 October 26 (Box 33, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0292)
    Cable13 tape number: Show Tape; Other notes: Show 1 guests: John Moore/ Tim Blitch (crew team), Highlights - football vs Maryland, soccer vs Wake Show 2 Chris Sercio, Crew Highlights, Water Polo highlights and guests
  - No Pretensions, 1986 October 29 (Box 32, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0293)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: #1; Other notes: Comedy News Show about National and Duke News (parody)
  - Fuqua Follies, 1986 November 01 (Box 31, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0280)
    Cable13 tape number: 2 (2)
  - Duke Magazine, 1986 November 03 (Box 29, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0281)
    Other notes: Pitchforks Fall Classic, Halloween, Sanford/Broyhill Poll
  - The Feud: ATO vs SAE, 1986 November 04 (Box 31, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0282)
    Other notes: ATO vs SAE (little sisters)
  - Sports Center, 1986 November 09 (Box 33, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0283)
    Program Length: 30mins48secs; Cable13 tape number: Show Tape; Other notes: guests - Tom Stone and John Koor, Highlights: football, basketball, volleyball and Soccer
  - Special Events: Neil Simon, 1986 November 10 (Box 35, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0284)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1); Other notes: Neil Simon, Gene Saks, Linda Lavin Produced by David Oelsner and Steve Tell
  - Sports Center, 1986 November 16, 1986 November 23 (Box 24, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0285)
    Cable13 tape number: L 13 / S6; Other notes: 11/16/86 Show #4 Joke, 11/23/86 Show #5
  - The Feud: Betas vs. Kappas, 1986 November 17, 1986 December 2 (Box 31, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0286)
    Cable13 tape number: 8801-3-208; Other notes: Producers: Rich Aldridge, Dan Treinish
  - NCAA Soccer: Duke vs State, 1986 November 23 (Box 34, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0287)
    Program Length: 20mins; Cable13 tape number: L3/S4
  - NCAA Soccer: Duke vs Akron, 1986 December 14 (Box 34, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0253)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 1; Other notes: First Half
  - NCAA Soccer: Duke vs Akron, 1986 December 14 (Box 34, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0254)
    Cable13 tape number: Tape 2; Other notes: Second Half, Championships
  - Cyrus X: The Movie, 1987 (Box 82, Video-cassette UA09130008-Bcam-0001)
    Program Length: 47mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (2); Other notes: Prod: Jim Balis, Stars: Christa Kirby, Mark Dorosin, Mike Adlin
  - Best of No Pretensions, 1987 (Box 25, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0034)
    Program Length: 15mins45secs; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-112; Other notes: Vol 1
  - Night Night, 1987 (Box 31, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0035)
    Program Length: 29mins&26mins; Cable13 tape number: #2 & #3; Other notes:
  - Night Night, 1987 (Box 31, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0036)
    Program Length: 29mins06secs; Cable13 tape number: #4
  - Night Night, 1987 (Box 104, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0037)
    Program Length: 35mins; Cable13 tape number: #7
  - Best of Night Night 1987 (Box 32, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0038)
    Program Length: 60mins
  - Night Night, 1987 (Box 37, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0039)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-143; Other notes: #1 The Election Newscast
  - Night Night #1, 1987 Fall (Box 37, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0324)
    Program Length: 30mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-120
  - Night Night #2, 1987 Fall (Box 37, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0325)
    Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-125
  - Night Night, 1987 Spring (Box 31, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0388)
    Program Length: 29mins&32mins; Cable13 tape number: #1 & #5; Other notes: Intro, Funniest Man in the World, Blake's storm hour, the encounter, the black eye news, beer commercial, quad squad #2
  - Night Night, 1987 Spring (Box 31, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0389)
    Program Length: 25mins; Cable13 tape number: #6
  - Night Night, 1987 Spring (Box 104, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0390)
    Program Length: 25mins; Cable13 tape number: #8; Other notes: SNL type show w/ restaurant and new scene, talking paintings, west side story, torture scene
  - Speakers: Shevchenko, 1987 Spring (Box 35, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0391)
    Other notes: no audio
  - The Best of Night Night, 1987 Spring (Box 35, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0392)
    Program Length: 32mins; Other notes: SNL show, quad squad, talking paintings, news, curb encounter, Grizlor master of the universe interview, mall interview
  - FuquaVision, 1987, 1993 (Box 65, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0393)
    Program Length: 55mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-6-100; Other notes: 11/8/87: (studio and CEO Disney) 00-17:35, 4/4/87: 17:35-31:31, 11/22/87: 31:31-55:00, 1/12/93 "The Grind"
  - Commercials Master Broadcast, 1987-1988 (Box 35, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0394)
    Program Length: 9mins10secs; Other notes: Video Virginity, volleyball, turn it on again, Bodyworks, what turns you on, easy answers, video personals, revote, cable 13 promo
  - Reel stories, 1987-1988 (Box 37, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0395)
    Program Length: 7mins13secs; Cable13 tape number: E 1; Other notes: Dramatic Short
  - Sports Center Sunday, 1987-1988 (Box 38, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0396)
    Cable13 tape number: 8708-6-091; Other notes: Show #2 Highlights Tape
  - Sports Center Sunday Hi-Lites, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0397)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: 8708-6-063; Other notes: Highlights tape #1
  - FuquaVision/MBA Games Titles, 1987-1988 (Box 43, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0398)
    Cable13 tape number: 8908-30-658
  - Duke Yearlook, 1987 (Box 95, Video-cassette UA09130008-VHS-0005)
  - Sports Center, 1987 January 18, 1987 February 01, 1987 February 08 (Box 33, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0342)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Show Tape; Other notes: Show #1 1/18: No host, UNC Basketball Highlights, Show#2 2/1: Billy Black, Show#3 2/8: Billy Black, highlights, MD & UVA slam dunk contest
  - No Pretensions, 1987 January 21 (Box 32, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0343)
    Cable13 tape number: #3; Other notes: Admissions Office Investigation, Crew: Steve Tell, Eric Jones, Liza Mortimer, Kym Contreras, Andy Landis, Lura Luther, Jeff Bass, Brad Kirby
  - Commercials Union Ad, 1987 January 26 (Box 18, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0344)
  - Special Events: Gary Hart, 1987 January 27 (Box 34, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0345)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: Tape 1 (1); Other notes: "Education: The Key to America's Third Century" Produced by Steve Tell, David Oelsner
  - Special Events: Gary Hart, 1987 January 27 (Box 34, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0346)
  - Cyrus X, 1987 January 28 (Box 30, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0347)
    Program Length: 60mins; Cable13 tape number: #8; Other notes: call-in show, pet lady
  - No Pretensions, 1987 February 03 (Box 32, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0326)
    Cable13 tape number: 8708-3-119; Other notes: opening, Stan & brad, bows, squirrels, coors, condoms, Bressler, Ted and Springfest, fluke, sigma Chris, Kipping, Ted & Charles, Craig-conservative corner
  - No Pretensions, 1987 February 03 (Box 32, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0327)
    Cable13 tape number: #4; Other notes: w/ Gary Hart
  - Basketball: Duke vs UVA, 1987 February 04 (Box 34, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0328)
    Program Length: 62mins20secs; Cable13 tape number: L13/S1 Tape 1 (2); Other notes:
  - Basketball: Duke vs UVA, 1987 February 04 (Box 34, Video-cassette UA09130008-Umatic-0329)